jackson.com 2007-12-30

# Jackson, Mississippi Guide to Local Hotels, Lodging, Restaurants, Real Estate, Car Rentals and Area Information

| 

Privacy Policy

We Local Matters, Inc. ("Local Matters"), the party that operates the webpage that you just linked from, respect the privacy of the visitors to our webpage ("Website"). This Privacy Policy is intended to inform you of our policies and practices regarding the collection, use and disclosure of any personal information you submit to us through our website. "Personal Information" is information about you that is personally identifiable to you like your name, address, email address, or phone number, as well as other non-public information that is associated with the foregoing. 

Your Consent 

By using our Website, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy and you expressly consent to the processing of your Personal Information according to this Privacy Policy. You should visit this page periodically to review any changes to this Privacy Policy. 

**Your Personal Information may be processed by Local Matters in the country where it was collected as well as other countries (including the United States) where laws regarding processing of Personal Information may be less stringent than the laws in your country.**

Your California Privacy Rights

Our customers who are California residents may request and obtain from us once a year, free of charge, certain information about the personal information (if any) we disclosed to third parties for direct marketing purposes in the preceding calendar year. If applicable, this information would include a list of the categories of personal information that was shared and the names and addresses of all third parties with which we shared information in the immediately preceding calendar year. If you are a California resident and would like to make such a request, please submit your request in writing to: 

Local Matters, Inc.  
Attention: Legal Affairs   
1221 Auraria Parkway   
Denver, CO 80204

Information We Collect 

We collect Personal Information that you submit to us voluntarily through our Website. If you create an account in order to access certain features and services, we may collect certain Personal Information such as your email address, a user name and password. If you email us directly via an e-mail hyperlink to provide us feedback or to ask us a question regarding the Website or our business, we will collect any information contained in such email, and we will treat any such information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. If you provide any such feedback to us, we may use such feedback for any purpose, provided we will not associate such feedback with your Personal Information. 

We will collect all information you submit via the Website, including any Personal Information. Please note that you are not obligated to provide any Personal Information to use the Website. 

If you decide to email search content to another person through the Website, we will collect that person's email address in order to send this email. We will also collect your name, email address, and any personal message you decide to include in the email. We will not send additional emails to this individual, unless you specifically request us to do so. 

We may request Personal Information for access to or use of certain services or features of the Website. As discussed in more detail below, our third party business partners may request Personal Information from you in order to provide you with information about goods or services, or to provide you with other information requested by you. You do not need to provide any requested Personal Information, but if you choose not to provide requested information, you may not be able to access or use those features or services. 

As you navigate our Website, certain information will also be collected passively by Local Matters or its service providers, including Internet Protocol addresses, search criteria, cookies and navigational data. This type of information is not Personal Information and will be used in the aggregate for the purposes of gathering data to improve our Website, and to improve the quality of your experience when interacting with our Website. This information will not be linked with any Personal Information. 

" **Cookies** " are small pieces of information that a web site sends to your computer's hard drive while you are viewing a web site. Local Matters may use both session Cookies (which expire once you close your web browser) and persistent Cookies (which stay on your computer until you delete them) to provide you with a more personal and interactive experience on the Website. Persistent Cookies can be removed by following Internet browser help file directions. If you choose to disable Cookies, some areas of the Website may not work properly. 

Our Business Partners 

Our third party business partners may collect information, including Personal Information, from various locations on the Website in order to provide you with information about their products and services, or to provide you with other requested information. Some third party business partners may request you to submit information by completing a form to receive more information about services or products offered by the business partners. The use of the information you provide to the third party business partner is subject to that business partner's privacy policy. 

We currently contract with third party business partners to help manage and optimize the Website and our Internet business. We use the services of a marketing company to help us measure the effectiveness of our advertising and how visitors use the Website. To do this, we use web beacons and cookies provided by our marketing company on this Website. This information helps us learn information about the use of the Website, including what pages are most attractive to our visitors, which of our services and products are of most interest to our visitors, and what types of offers our visitors like to see. Although our marketing company logs the information coming from our site on our behalf, we control how that data may and may not be used as described in this Privacy Policy. If you do not want to help us learn how to improve the Website, you can "opt-out" of this website analysis tool by clicking here: <http://www.omniture.com/privacy/product#optout>. 

How We Use Your Information

In general, Personal Information you submit to us is used to respond to requests that you make or to provide or improve our services. We will also use your Personal Information as directed by you. 

We may also use your email address to send you updates or news regarding our site, but you may choose not to receive email of this type upon sign-up. Despite your indicated email preferences, we may have to send you notices of any updates to our Terms of Service, Privacy Policy, or your account. 

Browser-type related information, IP address, requested URL, referring URL, and timestamp data help us diagnose problems with our server, administer, and otherwise provide the highest possible level of service to you. In addition, we use this information to perform statistical analyses of user behavior and characteristics in order to measure interest in and use of the various areas of the site and to inform advertisers of such information as well as the number of users that have been exposed to, or clicked on, their advertising banners. 

We may use third-party business partners to serve ads when you visit our Website. We may transfer to third party business partners or allow the collection by third party business partners of certain types of non-Personal Information for the purpose of providing you with advertisements on this Website and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please click here <http://www.zedo.com/company/optout.htm>.

Disclosure of Personal Information 

Except as set forth in this Privacy Policy, we do not sell, rent, share, trade or give away any of your Personal Information to third parties. We may disclose your Personal Information if we believe in good faith that such disclosure is necessary to (a) comply with relevant laws or to respond to subpoenas or warrants served on the Website; or (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Local Matters or any third party. We also share Personal Information that you voluntarily submit to us with our applicable third party business partner for the purpose for which you submitted the Personal Information. For example, if you wish to receive information from a third party business partner, and you provide Personal Information so that the business partner may contact you, we will share that Personal Information with the business partner. 

Although we currently do not have a parent company, any subsidiaries, joint ventures, or other companies under a common control (collectively, "related entities"), we may in the future. We may share some or all of your Personal Information with these related entities, in which case we will require our related entities to honor this Privacy Policy. If our company or our assets are acquired by another company, that company will possess the Personal Information collected by us and it will assume the rights and obligations regarding your Personal Information as described in this Privacy Policy. 

We will notify you when information about you may be provided to third parties in ways other than explained above, and you will have the option to prevent such information sharing. 

Links 

Our Website may contain links to third party websites to which we have no affiliation. Local Matters does not share your personal information with those websites and is not responsible for their privacy practices. We suggest you read the privacy polices on these third party websites. 

Your Choices Regarding Your Personal Information 

You should be aware that when you voluntarily disclose Personal Information (e.g., username, e-mail address) via emails, messages, postings, or in other areas of the Website, that information, along with any substantive information disclosed in your communication, can be collected and correlated and used by third parties and may result in unsolicited messages from other posters or third parties. Such activities are beyond the control of Local Matters. Please do not post any personal information on the Website or in other areas that you expect to keep private. 

Regarding Children 

We do not intentionally gather Personal Information about visitors who are under the age of 13 or any other age group. Should a child whom we know to be under 13 send personal information to us, we will use that information only to respond directly to that child (or a parent or guardian) to inform him or her that we must have parental consent before receiving his or her personal information. Should a child whom we know to be under 13 post Personal Information to our Website, we will delete any Personal Information that has been posted and either ask the child for a parent's email address for purposes of providing notice and obtaining consent to future postings, or take reasonable steps to block that child from using the Website, whether through screen name blocking, a cookie, or some other means. 

Security 

We use industry standard measures to maintain the security of your Personal Information. These measures include, but are not limited to, the use of a corporate firewall, storage of our software and servers in a secure co-location facility, and the requirement of password-protection on Personal Information. Although we take industry standard measures to safeguard against unauthorized disclosures of information, we cannot fully eliminate security risks associated with Personal Information 

You hereby acknowledge that Local Matters is not responsible for any intercepted information sent via the Internet, and you hereby release us from any and all claims arising out of or related to the use of intercepted information in any unauthorized manner. 

Privacy Policy Updates 

This Privacy Policy is maintained in conformance with applicable privacy laws and regulations, and is subject to occasional revision, and if we make any substantial changes in the way we collect, use, or disclose your Personal Information, we will post a notice on this page. If you object to any such changes, you must cease using our Website. Continued use of our Website following notice of any such changes shall indicate your acknowledgement of such changes and agreement to be bound by the terms and conditions of such changes. 

Contact Us 

Should you have any questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us: 

Local Matters, Inc.   
1221 Auraria Parkway   
Denver, CO 80204   

Last Updated: March 9, 2007
